{
  "isTheory": true,
  "openingRemarks": "Find the solution to the following equations",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "\\(-(s + 4) = 18 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n-(s + 4) &= 18 \\\\\n-s - 4 &= 18 \\\\\n-s &= 18 + 4 \\\\\n-s &= 22 \\\\\n\\dfrac{-s}{-1} &= \\dfrac{22}{-1} \\\\\ns &= -22\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 18</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(-(s+4)\\) if \\(s=-1\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n-(s + 4) &= -(-22 + 4) \\\\\n&= -(-18) \\\\\n&= 18 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(8 + 3(n - 9) = 17 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n8 + 3(n - 9) &= 17 \\\\\n8 + 3n - 27 &= 17 \\\\\n3n &= 17 + 27 - 8 \\\\\n3n &= 36 \\\\\n\\dfrac{3n}{3} &= \\dfrac{36}{3} \\\\\nn &= 12\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 17</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(8 + 3(n - 9)\\) if \\(n=12\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n8 + 3(n - 9) &= 8 + 3(12 - 9) \\\\\n&= 8 + 3(3) \\\\\n&= 8 + 9 \\\\\n&= 17\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(23 - 3(y - 7) = 8 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n23 - 3(y - 7) &= 8 \\\\\n23 - 3y + 21 &= 8 \\\\\n-3y &= 8 - 21 - 23 \\\\\n-3y &= -36 \\\\\n\\dfrac{-3y}{-3} &= \\dfrac{-36}{-3} \\\\\ny &= 12\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 8</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(23 - 3(y - 7)\\) if \\(y=12\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n23 - 3(y - 7) &= 23 - 3(12 - 7) \\\\\n&= 23 - 3(5) \\\\\n&= 23 - 15 \\\\\n&= 8\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{3}(6m + 21) = m - 7 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{1}{3}(6m + 21) &= m - 7 \\\\\n3 \\times \\dfrac{1}{3}(6m + 21) &= 3(m - 7) \\\\\n6m + 21 &= 3m - 21 \\\\\n6m - 3m &= -21 - 21 \\\\\n3m &= -42 \\\\\n\\dfrac{3m}{3} &= \\dfrac{-42}{3} \\\\\nm &= -14\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{1}{3}(6m + 21)\\) if \\(m=-14\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{1}{3}(6m + 21) &= \\dfrac{1}{3}(6(-14) + 21) \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{1}{3}(-84 + 21) \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{1}{3}(-63) \\\\\n&= -21\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n<div>Evaluate \\(m - 7\\) if \\(m=-14\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\nm - 7 &= -14 - 7 \\\\\n&= -21\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(8(r - 2) = 6(r + 10) \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n8(r - 2) &= 6(r + 10) \\\\\n8r - 16 &= 6r + 60 \\\\\n8r - 6r &= 60 + 16 \\\\\n2r = 76 \\\\\n\\dfrac{2r}{2} &= \\dfrac{76}{2} \\\\\nr &= 38\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(8(r - 2)\\) if \\(r=38\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n8(r - 2) &= 8(38 - 2) \\\\\n&= 8(36) \\\\\n&= 288\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n<div>Evaluate \\(6(r + 10)\\) if \\(r=38\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n6(r + 10) &= 6(38 + 10) \\\\\n&= 6(48) \\\\\n&= 288\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(5 + 7(2 - 5x) = 2(9x + 1) - (13x - 57) \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n5 + 7(2 - 5x) &= 2(9x + 1) - (13x - 57) \\\\\n5 + 14 - 35x &= 18x + 2 - 13x + 57 \\\\\n-35x - 18x + 13x &= 57 + 2 - 5 - 14 \\\\\n-40x = 40 \\\\\n\\dfrac{-40x}{-40} &= \\dfrac{40}{-40} \\\\\nx &= -1\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(5 + 7(2 - 5x)\\) if \\(x=-1\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n5 + 7(2 - 5x) &= 5 + 7(2 - 5(-1)) \\\\\n&= 5 + 7(2 + 5) \\\\\n&= 5 + 7(7) \\\\\n&= 5 + 49 \\\\\n&= 54\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n<div>Evaluate \\(2(9x + 1) - (13x - 57)\\) if \\(x=-1\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n2(9x + 1) - (13x - 57) &= 2(9(-1) + 1) - (13(-1) - 57) \\\\\n&= 2(-9 + 1) - (-13 - 57) \\\\\n&= 2(-8) - (-70) \\\\\n&= -16 + 70 \\\\\n&= 54\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(4(3.5y + 0.25) = 365 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n4(3.5y + 0.25) &= 365 \\\\\n14y + 1 &= 365 \\\\\n14y &= 365 - 1 \\\\\n14y = 364 \\\\\n\\dfrac{14y}{14} &= \\dfrac{364}{14} \\\\\ny &= 26\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 365</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(4(3.5y + 0.25)\\) if \\(y=26\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n4(3.5y + 0.25) &= 4(3.5(26) + 0.25) \\\\\n&= 4(91 + 0.25) \\\\\n&= 4(91.25) \\\\\n&= 365\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.25(q - 8) = 0.1(q + 7) \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n0.25(q - 8) &= 0.1(q + 7) \\\\\n0.25q - 2 &= 0.1q + 0.7 \\\\\n0.25q - 0.1q &= 0.7 + 2 \\\\\n0.15q = 2.7 \\\\\n\\dfrac{0.15q}{0.15} &= \\dfrac{2.7}{0.15} \\\\\nq &= 18\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(0.25(q - 8)\\) if \\(q=18\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n0.25(q - 8) &= 0.25(18 - 8) \\\\\n&= 0.25(10) \\\\\n&=2.5\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(0.1(q + 7)\\) if \\(q=18\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n0.1(q + 7) &= 0.1(18 + 7) \\\\\n&= 0.1(25) \\\\\n&=2.5\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{2}{5}n - \\dfrac{1}{10} = \\dfrac{7}{10} \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{2}{5}n - \\dfrac{1}{10} &= \\dfrac{7}{10} \\\\\n10 \\times \\dfrac{2}{5}n - 10 \\times \\dfrac{1}{10} &= 10 \\times \\dfrac{7}{10} \\\\\n2(2n) - 1 &= 7 \\\\\n4n = 7 + 1 \\\\\n4n &= 8 \\\\\n\\dfrac{4n}{4} &= \\dfrac{8}{4} \\\\\nn &= 2\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = \\(\\dfrac{7}{10}\\)</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{2}{5}n - \\dfrac{1}{10}\\) if \\(n=2\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{2}{5}n - \\dfrac{1}{10} &= \\dfrac{2}{5}(2) - \\dfrac{1}{10} \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{4}{5} - \\dfrac{1}{10} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{7}{10}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{3}x + \\dfrac{1}{5}x = 8 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{1}{3}x + \\dfrac{1}{5}x &= 8 \\\\\n15 \\times \\dfrac{1}{3}x + 15 \\times \\dfrac{1}{5}x &= 15 \\times 8 \\\\\n5x + 3x &= 120 \\\\\n8x &= 120 \\\\\n\\dfrac{8x}{8} &= \\dfrac{120}{8} \\\\\nx &= 15\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 8</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{1}{3}x + \\dfrac{1}{5}x\\) if \\(x=15\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{1}{3}x + \\dfrac{1}{5}x &= \\dfrac{1}{3}(15) + \\dfrac{1}{5}(15) \\\\\n&= 5 + 3 \\\\\n&= 8\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{3}{4}a - \\dfrac{1}{3} = \\dfrac{1}{2}a + \\dfrac{5}{6} \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{3}{4}a - \\dfrac{1}{3} &= \\dfrac{1}{2}a + \\dfrac{5}{6} \\\\\n12 \\times \\dfrac{3}{4}a - 12 \\times \\dfrac{1}{3} &= 12 \\times \\dfrac{1}{2}a + 12 \\times \\dfrac{5}{6} \\\\\n3 \\times 3a - 4 \\times 1 &= 6 \\times a + 2 \\times 5 \\\\\n9a - 4 &= 6a + 10 \\\\\n9a - 6a &= 10 + 4 \\\\\n3a &= 14 \\\\\n\\dfrac{3a}{3} &= \\dfrac{14}{3} \\\\\na &= \\dfrac{14}{3}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{3}{4}a - \\dfrac{1}{3}\\) if \\(a=\\dfrac{14}{3}\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{3}{4}a - \\dfrac{1}{3} &= \\dfrac{3}{4}\\left(\\dfrac{14}{3}\\right) - \\dfrac{1}{3} \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{7}{2} - \\dfrac{1}{3} \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{19}{6}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{1}{2}a + \\dfrac{5}{6}\\) if \\(a=\\dfrac{14}{3}\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{1}{2}a + \\dfrac{5}{6} &= \\dfrac{1}{2}\\left(\\dfrac{14}{3}\\right) + \\dfrac{5}{6} \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{7}{3} + \\dfrac{5}{6} \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{19}{6}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{2}(k+3) = \\dfrac{1}{3}(k + 16) \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{1}{2}(k+3) &= \\dfrac{1}{3}(k + 16) \\\\\n6 \\times \\dfrac{1}{2}(k + 3) &= 6 \\times \\dfrac{1}{3}(k + 16) \\\\\n3(k + 3) &= 2(k + 16) \\\\\n3k + 9 &= 2k + 32 \\\\\n3k - 2k &= 32 - 9 \\\\\nk &= 23\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{1}{2}(k+3)\\) if \\(k=23\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{1}{2}(k+3) &= \\dfrac{1}{2}(23+3) \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{1}{2}(26) \\\\\n&= 13\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{1}{3}(k+16)\\) if \\(k=23\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{1}{3}(k+16) &= \\dfrac{1}{3}(23+16) \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{1}{3}(39) \\\\\n&= 13\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.8x - 0.3 = 0.7x + 0.2 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n0.8x - 0.3 &= 0.7x + 0.2 \\\\\n0.8x - 0.7x &= 0.2 + 0.3 \\\\\n0.1x &= 0.5 \\\\\n\\dfrac{0.1x}{0.1} &= \\dfrac{0.5}{0.1} \\\\\nx &= 5\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(0.8x - 0.3\\) if \\(x=-5\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n0.8x - 0.3 &= 0.8(5) - 0.3 \\\\\n&= 4 - 0.3 \\\\\n&= 3.7\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(0.7x + 0.2\\) if \\(x=5\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n0.7x + 0.2 &= 0.7(5) + 0.2 \\\\\n&= 3.5 + 0.2 \\\\\n&= 3.7\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.36a + 2.55 = 0.41a + 6.8 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n0.36a + 2.55 &= 0.41a + 6.8 \\\\\n0.36a - 0.41a &= 6.8 - 2.55 \\\\\n-0.05a &= 4.25 \\\\\n\\dfrac{-0.05a}{-0.05} &= \\dfrac{4.25}{-0.05} \\\\\na &= -85\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(0.36a + 2.55\\) if \\(a=-85\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n0.36a + 2.55 &= 0.36(-85) + 2.55 \\\\\n&= -30.6 + 2.55 \\\\\n&= -28.05\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(0.41a + 6.8\\) if \\(a=-85\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n0.41a + 6.8 &= 0.41(-85) + 6.8 \\\\\n&= -34.85 + 6.8 \\\\\n&= -28.05\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.6p - 1.9 = 0.78p + 1.7 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n0.6p - 1.9 &= 0.78p + 1.7 \\\\\n0.6p - 0.78p &= 1.7 + 1.9 \\\\\n-0.18p &= 3.6 \\\\\n\\dfrac{-0.18p}{-0.18} &= \\dfrac{3.6}{-0.18} \\\\\np &= -20\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(0.6p - 1.9\\) if \\(p=-20\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n0.6p - 1.9 &= 0.6(-20) - 1.9 \\\\\n&= -12 - 1.9 \\\\\n&= -13.9\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(0.78p + 1.7\\) if \\(p=-20\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n0.78p + 1.7 &= 0.78(-20) + 1.7 \\\\\n&= -15.6 + 1.7 \\\\\n&= -13.9\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.10d + 0.05(d - 4) = 2.05 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n0.10d + 0.05(d - 4) &= 2.05 \\\\\n0.10d + 0.05d - 0.2 &= 2.05 \\\\\n0.15d &= 2.05 + 0.2 \\\\\n0.15d &= 2.25 \\\\\n\\dfrac{0.15d}{0.15} &= \\dfrac{2.25}{0.15} \\\\\nd &= 15\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 2.05</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(0.10d + 0.05(d - 4)\\) if \\(d=15\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n0.10d + 0.05(d - 4) &= 0.10(15) + 0.05(15 - 4) \\\\\n&= 1.5 + 0.05(11) \\\\\n&= 1.5 + 0.55 \\\\\n&= 2.05 \n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(n - 18 = 31 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\nn - 18 &= 31 \\\\\nn &= 31 + 18 \\\\\nn &= 49\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 31</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(n - 18\\) if \\(n=49\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\nn - 18 &= 49 - 18 \\\\\n&= 31\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(9c = 144 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n9c &= 144 \\\\\n\\dfrac{9c}{9} &= \\dfrac{144}{9} \\\\\nc &= 16\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 144</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(9c\\) if \\(c=16\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n9c &= 9(16) \\\\\n&= 144\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(4y - 8 = 16 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n4y - 8 &= 16 \\\\\n4y &= 16 + 8 \\\\\n4y &= 24 \\\\\n\\dfrac{4y}{4} &= \\dfrac{24}{4} \\\\\ny &= 6\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 16</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(4y - 8\\) if \\(y=6\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n4y - 8 &= 4(6) - 8 \\\\\n&= 24 - 8 \\\\\n&= 16\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-8x - 15 + 9x - 1 = -21 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n-8x - 15 + 9x - 1 &= -21 \\\\\n-8x + 9x &= -21 + 15 + 1 \\\\\nx &= -5\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = -21</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(-8x - 15 + 9x - 1\\) if \\(x=-5\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n-8x - 15 + 9x - 1 &= -8(-5) - 15 + 9(-5) - 1 \\\\\n&= 40 - 15- 45 - 1 \\\\\n&= -21\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-15a = 120 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n-15a &= 120 \\\\\n\\dfrac{-15a}{-15} &= \\dfrac{120}{-15} \\\\\na &= -8\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 120</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(-15a\\) if \\(a=-8\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n-15a &= -15(-8) \\\\\n&= 120\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{2}{3}x = 6 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{2}{3}x &= 6 \\\\\n3 \\times \\dfrac{2}{3}x &= 3 \\times 6 \\\\\n2x &= 18 \\\\\n\\dfrac{2x}{2} &= \\dfrac{18}{2} \\\\\nx &= 9\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 6</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{2}{3}x\\) if \\(x=9\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{2}{3}x &= \\dfrac{2}{3}(9) \\\\\n&= 6\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(x + 3.8 = 8.2 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\nx + 3.8 &= 8.2 \\\\\nx &= 8.2 - 3.8 \\\\\nx &= 4.4\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 8.2</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(x + 3.8\\) if \\(x=4.4\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\nx + 3.8 &= 4.4 + 3.8 \\\\\n&= 8.2\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(10y = -5y + 60 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n10y &= -5y + 60 \\\\\n10y + 5y &= 60 \\\\\n15y &= 60 \\\\\n\\dfrac{15y}{15} &= \\dfrac{60}{15} \\\\\ny &= 4\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(10y\\) if \\(y=4\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n10y &= 10(4) \\\\\n&= 40\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(-5y + 60\\) if \\(y=4\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n-5y + 60 &= -5(4) + 60 \\\\\n&= -20 + 60 \\\\\n&= 40\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(8n + 2 = 6n + 12 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n8n + 2 &= 6n + 12 \\\\\n8n - 6n &= 12 -2 \\\\\n2n &= 10 \\\\\n\\dfrac{2n}{2} &= \\dfrac{10}{2} \\\\\nn &= 5\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(8n + 2\\) if \\(n=5\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n8n + 2 &= 8(5) + 2 \\\\\n&= 40 + 2 \\\\\n&= 42\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(6n + 12\\) if \\(n=5\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n6n + 12 &= 6(5) + 12 \\\\\n&= 30 + 12 \\\\\n&= 42\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(9m - 2 - 4m + m = 42 - 8 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n9m - 2 - 4m + m &= 42 - 8 \\\\\n9m - 4m + m &= 42 -8+2 \\\\\n6m &= 36 \\\\\n\\dfrac{6m}{6} &= \\dfrac{36}{6} \\\\\nm &= 6\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 34</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(9m - 2 - 4m + m\\) if \\(m=6\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n9m - 2 - 4m + m &= 9(6) - 2 - 4(6) + 6 \\\\\n&= 54 - 2 - 24 + 6 \\\\\n&= 34\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-5(2x + 1) = 45 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n-5(2x + 1) &= 45 \\\\\n-10x - 5 &= 45 \\\\\n-10x &= 45 + 5 \\\\\n-10x &= 50 \\\\\n\\dfrac{-10x}{-10} &= \\dfrac{50}{-10} \\\\\nx &= -5\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 45</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(-5(2x + 1)\\) if \\(x=-5\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n-5(2x + 1) &= -5(2(-5) + 1) \\\\\n&= -5(-10 + 1) \\\\\n&= -5(-9) \\\\\n&= 45\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-(d + 9) = 23 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n-(d + 9) &= 23 \\\\\n-d - 9 &= 23 \\\\\n-d &= 23 + 9 \\\\\n-d &= 32 \\\\\n\\dfrac{-d}{-1} &= \\dfrac{32}{-1} \\\\\nd &= -32\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 23</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(-(d + 9)\\) if \\(d=-32\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n-(d + 9) &= -(-32 + 9) \\\\\n&= -(-23) \\\\\n&= 23\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2(6x+ 5) - 8 = -22 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n2(6x+ 5) - 8 &= -22 \\\\\n12x + 10 - 8 &= -22 \\\\\n12x &= -22 + 8 - 10 \\\\\n12x &= -24 \\\\\n\\dfrac{12x}{12} &= \\dfrac{-24}{12} \\\\\nx &= -2\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = -22</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(2(6x+ 5) - 8\\) if \\(x=-2\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n2(6x+ 5) - 8 &= 2(6(-2) + 5) - 8 \\\\\n&= 2(-12 + 5) - 8 \\\\\n&= 2(-7) - 8 \\\\\n&= -14 - 8 \\\\\n&= -22\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(8(3a + 5) - 7(4a - 3) = 20 - 3a \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n8(3a + 5) - 7(4a - 3) &= 20 - 3a \\\\\n24a + 40 - 28a + 21 &= 20 - 3a \\\\\n24a - 28a + 3a &= 20 - 21 - 40 \\\\\n-a &= -41 \\\\\n\\dfrac{-a}{-1} &= \\dfrac{-41}{-1} \\\\\na &= 41\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(8(3a + 5) - 7(4a - 3)\\) if \\(a=41\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n8(3a + 5) - 7(4a - 3) &= 8(3(41) + 5) - 7(4(41) - 3) \\\\\n&= 8(123 + 5) -7(164 - 3) \\\\\n&= 8(128) - 7(161) \\\\\n&= -1024 - 1127 \\\\\n&= -103\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(20 -3a\\) if \\(a=41\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n20 -3a &= 20 - 3(41) \\\\\n&= 20 - 123 \\\\\n&= -103\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{4}p + \\dfrac{1}{3} = \\dfrac{1}{2} \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{1}{4}p + \\dfrac{1}{3} &= \\dfrac{1}{2} \\\\\n12 \\times \\dfrac{1}{4}p + 12 \\times \\dfrac{1}{3} &= 12 \\times \\dfrac{1}{2} \\\\\n3p + 4 &= 6 \\\\\n3p &= 6 - 4 \\\\\n3p &= 2 \\\\\n\\dfrac{3p}{3} &= \\dfrac{2}{3} \\\\\np &= \\dfrac{2}{3}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = \\(\\dfrac{1}{2}\\)</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{1}{4}p + \\dfrac{1}{3}\\) if \\(p=\\dfrac{2}{3}\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{1}{4}p + \\dfrac{1}{3} &= \\dfrac{1}{4}\\left(\\dfrac{2}{3}\\right) + \\dfrac{1}{3} \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{1}{6} + \\dfrac{1}{3} \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{1}{2}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.1d + 0.25(d + 8) = 4.1 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n0.1d + 0.25(d + 8) &= 4.1 \\\\\n0.1d + 0.25d + 2 &= 4.1 \\\\\n0.1d + 0.25d &= 4.1 - 2 \\\\\n0.35d &= 2.1 \\\\\n\\dfrac{0.35d}{0.35} &= \\dfrac{2.1}{0.35} \\\\\nd &= 6\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 4.1</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(0.1d + 0.25(d + 8)\\) if \\(d=6\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n0.1d + 0.25(d + 8) &= 0.1(6) + 0.25(6 + 8) \\\\\n&= 0.6 + 0.25(14) \\\\\n&= 0.6 + 3.5 \\\\\n&= 4.1\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    }
  ]
}
